Guide to the Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature, 1936-2014 and undated RL.00045
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Caribbean, 1947-2006 and undated; 5; 13 boxes
  - Jamaica, 89
    - Hotels/Resorts--Negril--Swept Away, 1990-1996 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Ocho Rios, 1984-2003 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Ocho Rios, 1984-2003 and undated (Box CAR9)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Port Antonio, 1986-1996 and undated (Box CAR9)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Runaway Bay, 1983 and undated (Box CAR9)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Super Clubs, 1994-2003; 2 folders (Box CAR9)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Villas, 1984-2004 and undated (Box CAR9)
  - Martinique, 90
    - General, 1968-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR9)
  - Miscellaneous islands, 91
    - General, 1967-1972 and undated (Box CAR9)
  - Montserrat, 92
    - General, 1993 and undated (Box CAR9)
  - Mustique, 93
    - General, 1981-2004 and undated (Box CAR9)
  - Nevis, 94
    - General, 1997-2005 and undated (Box CAR9)
  - Puerto Rico, 95
    - General, 1962-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box CAR10)
    - Hotels/Resorts, 1994-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR10)
  - St. Barthelemy, 96
    - General, 1994-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR10)
  - St. Eustatius, 97
    - General, 1983-1986 and undated (Box CAR11)
  - St. Kitts, 98
    - General, 1983-1992 and undated (Box CAR11)
  - St. Lucia, 99
    - General, 1969-1974 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR11)
    - Hotels/Resorts, 1991-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR11)
  - St. Maartin/Sint Maartin, 100
    - General, 1970-1995 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR11)
  - St. Martin, 101
    - General, 1974-1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR11)
    - Hotels/Resorts, 1985-2003 and undated (Box CAR11)
    - Villas, undated (Box CAR11)
  - St. Vincent, 102
    - General, 1983-2004 and undated (Box CAR11)
  - Trinidad & Tobago, 103
    - General, 1958-1971 and undated (Box CAR11)
    - General, 1992-1996 and undated (Box CAR12)
    - Hotels, 1972-2005 and undated (Box CAR12)
  - Turks & Caicos, 104
    - General, 1984-2004 and undated (Box CAR12)
  - Vieques, 105
    - Hotels, undated (Box CAR12)
  - Virgin Islands (British), 106
    - General, 1992-2003 and undated (Box CAR12)
    - Guana, 1981-1992 and undated (Box CAR12)
    - Necker Island, 1986-2002 and undated (Box CAR12)
    - Peter Island, 2004 and undated (Box CAR12)
    - Tortola, 1969-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR12)
    - Virgin Gorda, 1972-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box CAR12)
  - Virgin Islands (U.S.), 107
    - General, 1979-2001 and undated (Box CAR13)
    - St. Croix, 1962-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR13)
    - St. Croix--Hotels, 1972-1996 and undated (Box CAR13)
    - St. John, 1972-2001 and undated (Box CAR13)
    - St. John--Caneel Bay, 1988-2004 and undated (Box CAR13)
    - St. Thomas, 1963-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR13)
    - St. Thomas--Hotels/Resorts, 1986-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR13)
- Central America, 1958-2006 and undated; 6; 2 boxes
  - General Files, 108
    - General, 1979-2006 and undated; 2 folders (Box CEN1)
  - Belize, 109
    - General, 1988-2004 and undated (Box CEN1)
    - Ambergris Caye, 1992-2003 (Box CEN1)
    - Francis Ford Coppola Resorts, 2002-2004 (Box CEN1)
    - Hotels and resorts, 1992-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box CEN1)
  - Costa Rica, 110
    - General, 1980-2004 and undated (Box CEN1)
    - Adventure/Cruise/Safari/Sport vacations, 1986-2000 and undated (Box CEN1)
    - Hotels, 1984-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box CEN1)
    - Travel planning, 1991-2005 (Box CEN1)
  - El Salvador, 111
    - General, 1969-2001 and undated (Box CEN2)
  - Guatemala, 112
    - General, 1958-1995 and undated; 2 folders (Box CEN2)
    - Magnificent Mystery: Tikal; The Mayan Mystery (Dale Nichols), 1970-1973 (Box CEN2)
  - Honduras, 113
    - General, 1976-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box CEN2)
  - Nicaragua, 114
    - General, undated (Box CEN2)
  - Panama, 115
    - General, 1964-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box CEN2)
- Europe, 1956-2007 and undated; 7; 60 boxes
  - General Files, 116
    - Ambercrombie & Kent, 2005 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Car rentals, 1988-1999 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Car rentals--Auto Europe, 1983-2005 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Car rentals--Carey Chauffeur Service, 1980-2002 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Car rentals--Hertz, 1995-2005 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Car rentals--Kremwel, 1983 (Box EUR1)
    - European Incoming Services, 2004-2005 and undated (Box EUR1)
    - Frame's National, 1984-1988 (Box EUR1)
    - Hotel guides, 1985-2002 (Box EUR1)
    - Hotel guides--Minotel, 1996 (Box EUR1)
    - Maps, 1995-2004 and undated (Box EUR2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-2000 and undated (Box EUR2)
    - Rail lines, 1961-2005 and undated (Box EUR2)
    - Tours and cruises, 1975-1984 (Box EUR2)
    - Travel guides, 1983 and undated (Box EUR2)
  - Austria, 117
    - General, 1977-2006 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR2)
    - Destinations, 1975-1987 and undated (Box EUR2)
    - Hotels, undated (Box EUR3)
    - Opera, 1992-2005 (Box EUR3)
    - Travel guides, 1982-2007 and undated (Box EUR3)
    - Innsbruck/Tirol, 1984-1989 and undated (Box EUR3)
    - Salzburg, 1982-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR3)
    - Salzburg--Hotels, 1969-1997 and undated (Box EUR3)
    - Vienna, 1977-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR3)
    - Vienna--Hotels, 1975-1996 and undated (Box EUR3)
  - Belgium, 118
    - General, 1975-1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR4)
    - Antwerp, 1985-1990 (Box EUR4)
    - Bruges, 1988-1995 and undated (Box EUR4)
    - Brussels, 1966-1994 and undated (Box EUR4)
  - Bulgaria, 119
    - Hotels, undated (Box EUR4)
  - Czechoslovakia/Czech Republic, 120
    - General, 1990-1991 (Box EUR4)
    - Prague, 1989-2005 and undated (Box EUR4)
  - Croatia, 121
    - General, 2005 and undated (Box EUR4)
  - Cyprus, 122
    - General, 1986-2004 and undated (Box EUR4)
  - France, 123
    - General, 1977 and undated (Box EUR4)
    - General--Articles, 1960-2004 and undated (Box EUR4)
    - General-Barge/Cruises, 1969-2006 and undated (Box EUR5)
    - General--Barge/Cruises--ResidenSea, 2002 (Box EUR5)
    - General--Chateau/Hotels, 1970-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR5)
    - General--Chateau/Hotels--Thoiry, 1986-1987 and undated (Box EUR5)
    - General--Focus on France (publication), 1989-2001 (Box EUR5)
    - General--Gite Rural (green/ecotourism), 1984 (Box EUR5)
    - General--Hotel directories, 1984-1998 and undated (Box EUR5)
    - General--Hotel directories, 1984-1998 and undated (Box EUR6)
    - General--Maps, 1966-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR6)
    - General--Photographs (includes BordeauxBiarritzEugenie de Bains), undated (Box EUR6)
    - General--Spas, 1987-2003 and undated (Box EUR6)
    - General--Tourist guides, 1975-2002 and undated (Box EUR6)
    - General--Tourist guides, 1975-2002 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - General--Transportation and touring services, 1973-2003 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - General--Wine and food tours, 1969-1995 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - General--Youth tourism, 1982-1998 (Box EUR7)
    - Alsace, 1984-2001 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - Aquitaine, 1993-2002 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - Avignon, 1985-2000 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - Basque country, 1966-1984 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - Bordeaux, 1983-1999 and undated (Box EUR7)
    - Brittany/Bretagne, 1997-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR7)
    - Burgundy/Bourgogne, 1987-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR8)
    - Carcassonne, 1995-2002 and undated (Box EUR8)
    - Champagne/Ardenne, 1993-1996 (Box EUR8)
    - Chartres, 1993 and undated (Box EUR8)
    - Corsica, circa 1971 and undated (Box EUR8)
    - Dordogne/Perigord, 1970-2000 and undated (Box EUR8)
    - Fontainbleau, 1986-1990 and undated (Box EUR8)
    - French Alps, 1980-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR8)
    - Gironde, 1960-2002 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Giverny, undated (Box EUR9)
    - Languedoc-Roussillon, 1970-2001 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Loire, 1974-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR9)
    - Lyon, 1992-2005 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Margeaux/Medoc, 2002 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Marseilles, undated (Box EUR9)
    - Midi/Pyrenees, 1985-2001 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Mougins, undated (Box EUR9)
    - Normandy, 1974-2003 and undated (Box EUR9)
    - Normandy, 1974-2003 and undated (Box EUR10)
    - Normandy--History/WWII, 1981-2002 and undated (Box EUR10)
    - Normandy--Hotels, 1984-2002 and undated (Box EUR10)
    - Normandy--Sightseeing, 1981-2004 and undated (Box EUR10)
    - Paris, 1982-1988 (Box EUR10)
    - Paris--Hotel directories, 1957-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR10)
    - Paris--Hotels A-G, 1987-2005 and undated (Box EUR10)
    - Paris--Hotels--Ambassador, 1995-2005 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Aubusson, 2005 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Bel Ami, 2005 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Bristol, 2005 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Concord, 1993-1999 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Crillon, 1994-2004 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--George V/Four Seasons, 2003-2004 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels H-M, 1996-2004 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Lancaster, 1970-2003 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Le Parc, 1996-1997 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Louvre, 1996-2004 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Lutetia, 1999-2005 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Meurice, 1984-2001 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels N-P, 1987-2006 and undated (Box EUR11)
    - Paris--Hotels--Plaza Athenee, undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--Pont Royal, 1970-2005 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels R-T, 1983-2001 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--Ritz, 1991-2025 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--Royal Monceau, 2002 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--San Regis, 1992-2007 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--Small Luxury Hotels, 1983-2005 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels--Tremoille, 1970-2005 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Hotels U-Z, 1973-2005 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Maps, 1981-2005 and undated (Box EUR12)
    - Paris--Outskirts (includes Ile de FranceVersailles), 1971-2002 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Paris--Sightseeing, 1981-2001 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Paris--Tourist guides, 1968-2004 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Paris--Transportation and tour operators, 1982-2004 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Picardy, 1975 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Provence, 1974-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR13)
    - Provence--Aix, 2002 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Provence--Bouches du Rhone, 1982-1995 and undated (Box EUR13)
    - Provence--Hotels, 1971-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR14)
    - Rhone, 1978-2005 and undated (Box EUR14)
    - Riviera, 1987-2005 and undated (Box EUR14)
    - Riviera--Biarritz, 1984-2001 and undated (Box EUR14)
    - Riviera--Cannes, 1984-2003 and undated (Box EUR14)
    - Riviera--Cote d'Azur, 1982-2004 and undated (Box EUR14)
    - Riviera--Cote d'Azur, 1982-2004 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - Riviera--Eze/St. Paul, 1993-1997 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - Riviera--Nice, 1970-2005 (Box EUR15)
    - Riviera--Nice Visitors Bureau, 1998 (Box EUR15)
    - Riviera--St. Tropez, 1990-2002 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - Saint-Germain-en-Laye, 1993-2004 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - St. Pierre, 1986 (Box EUR15)
    - Strasbourg, 1982 and undated (Box EUR15)
  - Germany, 124
    - General, 1968-2004 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - General--Hotel directories, 1984-2004 (Box EUR15)
    - General--Hotels, 1967-2004 and undated (Box EUR15)
    - General--Lufthansa publications, 1984-1987 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - General--Maps, 1981-2002 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - General--Spas/health resorts, undated (Box EUR16)
    - General--The Romantic Road, 1989 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - General--Travel planning, 1985-2004 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - Baden-Baden, 1969-2004 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - Berlin--Hotel directory, 2004 (Box EUR16)
    - Berlin--Hotels, 1985-2005 and undated (Box EUR16)
    - Berlin--Hotels, 1985-2005 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Berlin--Sightseeing, 1990-2004 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Bremen, 1985-1994 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Frankfurt, 1980-1998 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Friedrichsruhe, 1963-1982 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Garmisch-Partenkirchen, 1962-1989 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Hamburg, 1976-2004 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Heidelburg, 1975-1991 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Koln/Cologne, 1970-1999 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Munich, 1975-1996 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Munich--Hotels, 1970-2005 and undated (Box EUR17)
    - Rothenburg ob der Tauber, 1974-1998 and undated (Box EUR17)
  - Gibraltar, 125
    - General, 1987 and undated (Box EUR17)
  - Greece, 126
    - General, 1956-2004 and undated; 4 folders (Box EUR18)
    - General--Cruises, 1983-1984 (Box EUR18)
    - General--Hotels, 1972-1999 and undated (Box EUR18)
    - General--Maps, 1995-2004 and undated (Box EUR18)
    - General--Yachts, 1986-1991 (Box EUR18)
    - Athens/Attica, 1963-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR18)
    - Athens/Attica--Hotels, 1977-1994 and undated (Box EUR18)
    - Corfu, 1963-1993 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR18)
    - Crete--Hotels, 1983-1995 and undated (Box EUR18)
    - Crete--Tourist guides, 1981-1995 (Box EUR19)
    - Islands, 1984-1995 (Box EUR19)
    - Macedonia/Thrace, 1984-1993 (Box EUR19)
    - Miscellaneous destinations, 1978-1993 (Box EUR19)
    - Mykonos/Santorini, 1987 and undated (Box EUR19)
    - Peloponnese, 1983-1992 and undated (Box EUR19)
    - Rhodes, 1963-1969 and undated (Box EUR19)
  - Hungary, 127
    - General, 1969-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR19)
  - Iceland, 128
    - General, 2002-2004 and undated (Box EUR19)
  - Ireland (see also United Kingdom), 129
    - General, 1967-1981 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR19)
    - General, 1990-2000 and undated (Box EUR20)
    - Castle hotels, 1996-1997 and undated (Box EUR20)
    - Connoisseur's Guide to Ireland, undated (Box EUR20)
    - Country houses, 1973-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR20)
    - Golf, 1988-2002 and undated (Box EUR20)
    - Hotels, 1987-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR20)
    - Hotels--Dublin, 1986-2001 and undated (Box EUR20)
    - Hotels--Killarney Park, undated (Box EUR21)
    - Hotels--Mount Juliet, 2001-2002 and undated (Box EUR21)
    - Hotels--Park Hotel Kenmare, 1999 and undated (Box EUR21)
    - Hotels--Sheen Falls Lodge, 1996-2005 (Box EUR21)
    - Northern Ireland, 1968-1993 and undated (Box EUR21)
    - Tourist information, 1976-1998 and undated (Box EUR21)
    - Transportation and maps, 1973-2000 and undated (Box EUR21)
  - Italy, 130
    - General, 1958-1983 and undated (Box EUR21)
    - General, 1958-1983 and undated (Box EUR22)
    - General--Hotel directories, 1987-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR22)
    - General--Hotels, 1966-2004 and undated (Box EUR22)
    - General--Interhome rentals, 1992 and undated (Box EUR22)
    - General--Maps, 1956-1990 and undated (Box EUR22)
    - General--Spas, 1979-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR22)
    - General--Tourist guides, 1962-1998 and undated (Box EUR23)
    - General--Travel planning, 1982-2002; 2 folders (Box EUR23)
    - General--Villas and farmhouses, 2001-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR23)
    - General--Villas--Palladian, 1979-1993 and undated (Box EUR23)
    - Destinations, 1979-1987 and undated (Box EUR23)
    - Destinations--Ruins, 1983 and undated (Box EUR23)
    - Amalfi, 1988-2005 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Assisi, 1985-1987 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Bari, 2005 (Box EUR24)
    - Bellagio, 1987 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Bologna, 1973-1984 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Capri, 1974-1994 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Cinque Terre, 1991-2002 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Como, 1999-2005 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Como/Villa d'Este, 1955-2005 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Cortina, 1971-1985 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Costa Smeralda/Sardegne (Sardinia), 1967-1977 and undated (Box EUR24)
    - Dolomites/Dolomiti, 1970-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR24)
    - Erbusco, 2001-2005 (Box EUR24)
    - Ferrara, undated (Box EUR25)
    - Fiesole, 2003 (Box EUR25)
    - Firenze/Florence, 1965-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR25)
    - Firenze/Florence--Hotels A-P, 1991-2003 and undated; 5 folders (Box EUR25)
    - Firenze/Florence--Hotels--Palazzo Magnani Feroni, 2001-2004 and undated (Box EUR25)
    - Firenze/Florence--Hotels--R-Z, 1985-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR26)
    - Genoa/Genova, 1966-2001 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Gubbio--Hotels, undated (Box EUR26)
    - Isola d'Ischia, 1966-2005 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Lago di Como, 1966-1973 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Lago di Gardia/Sirmione, 1970-1994 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR26)
    - Lago d'Iseo, 1997 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Lago Maggiore/Stresa, 1959-1981 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Lazio/Latium, 1985-1998 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Lucca/Pietrasanta, undated (Box EUR26)
    - Maggiore, 2004 (Box EUR26)
    - Marche, 2004 and undated (Box EUR26)
    - Milan/Milano, 1984-2000 (Box EUR27)
    - Milan/Milano--Hotels, 1990-2005 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Milan/Milano--Hotels--Baglioni, undated (Box EUR27)
    - Milan/Milano--Hotels--Excelsior Gallia, 1985 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Milan/Milano--Hotels--Four Seasons, 1992-2003 (Box EUR27)
    - Milan/Milano--Hotels--Sheraton/Sina, 1996-1998 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Naples/Napoli, 1974-2001 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Novarra, 1979 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Orvieto, 2005 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Padua/Padova, 1995-1997 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Parma, 1966 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Pension, undated (Box EUR27)
    - Perugia, 1980-2005 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Pisa, 1987 and undated (Box EUR27)
    - Portofino, 1998-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR28)
    - Positano, 1973-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR28)
    - Posta Vecchia, 1993-2004 and undated (Box EUR28)
    - Rapallo, 2000 and undated (Box EUR28)
    - Ravello/Salerno, 1982-2005 and undated (Box EUR28)
    - Rimini, undated (Box EUR28)
    - Riviera, undated, 2 folders (Box EUR28)
    - Roma/Rome, 1998-2005 (Box EUR28)
    - Roma/Rome --Hotels A-E, 1988-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR28)
    - Roma/Rome--Hotels--Excelsior, 1996-2005 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Roma/Rome--Hotels F-R, 1997-2004 and undated; 4 folders (Box EUR29)
    - Roma/Rome--Hotel de Russie, 2000-2001 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Roma/Rome--Hotels S-V, 2002-2005 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Salerno, 1982-1987 (Box EUR29)
    - San Gimignano, undated (Box EUR29)
    - San Remo, 1994-1996 (Box EUR29)
    - Santa Margherita Ligure/Golfo Tigullo, 1967-1996 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR29)
    - Sardinia/Sardegna, 1965-1988 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Sardinia/Sardegna--Hotels, 1980-2001 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Sardinia/Sardegna--Hotels--Forte Village, 1983-2004 and undated (Box EUR29)
    - Sicily/Sicilia, 1957-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR30)
    - Sicily/Sicilia--Hotels, 1987-2002 and undated (Box EUR30)
    - Siena, 1981-1985 and undated (Box EUR30)
    - Siena--Hotels, 1996-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR30)
    - Sorrento, 1967-2005 and undated (Box EUR30)
    - Spoleto, undated (Box EUR30)
    - Stresa/Des Iles Borromes, undated (Box EUR30)
    - Torgiano, 2001 and undated (Box EUR30)
    - Treviso, undated (Box EUR30)
    - Trieste, undated (Box EUR30)
    - Turin/Torino, 1967-1990 and undated (Box EUR31)
    - Tuscany/Toscano, 1985-2005 and undated (Box EUR31)
    - Umbria, 2001 and undated (Box EUR31)
    - Venice/Venezio/Veneto, 1967-1984 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR31)
    - Venice/Venezio/Veneto--Hotels A-L, 1984-2005 and undated; 4 folders (Box EUR31)
    - Venice/Venezio/Veneto--Hotels--Londra Palace, 1998 and undated (Box EUR31)
    - Venice/Venezio/Veneto--Hotels M-Z, 1974-2005 and undated (Box EUR31)
    - Venice/Venezio/Veneto--Hotels--Villas, 1990-2001 (Box EUR32)
    - Verona, 1982-2003 and undated (Box EUR32)
    - Viareggio, 1987 and undated (Box EUR32)
  - Luxemburg, 131
    - General, 1966-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR32)
    - Hotels and restaurants, 1967-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR32)
  - Malta/Maltese Islands, 132
    - General, 1957-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR32)
  - Monaco/Monte Carlo, 133
    - General, 1985-2005 and undated (Box EUR32)
    - Hotels, 1971-2005 and undated (Box EUR32)
    - Hotels A-Z, 1969-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR33)
  - Netherlands/Holland, 134
    - General, 1959-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR33)
    - Hotels, 1972-1999 and undated (Box EUR33)
  - Poland, 135
    - General, 1972-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR33)
  - Portugal, 136
    - General, 1966-1984 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR33)
    - General, 1969-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR34)
    - General--Air Portugal conference information, undated (Box EUR34)
    - General--Golf, 1967-1996 and undated (Box EUR34)
    - General--Hotels, undated (Box EUR34)
    - General--Pousadas, 1984-2001 and undated (Box EUR34)
    - Destinations, 1977-1999 and undated (Box EUR34)
    - Algarve, 1966-2003 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR35)
    - Azores, 2004-2006 and undated (Box EUR35)
    - Estoril, 1962-1973 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR35)
    - Jewish Portugal, 1998 (Box EUR35)
    - Lisbon/Lisboa, 1963-2003 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR35)
    - Lisbon/Lisboa--Hotels, 1983-2004 and undated (Box EUR36)
    - Luso Bussaco/Bucaco, undated (Box EUR36)
    - Madeira, 1976-2003 and undated (Box EUR36)
    - Porto/Oporto, 1978-2001 and undated (Box EUR36)
  - Russia/Soviet Union, 137
    - General, 1990-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR36)
    - Moscow, undated (Box EUR36)
  - Scandinavia, 138
    - General, 1962-2002 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR36)
    - Cruise lines, undated (Box EUR36)
    - Denmark, 1959-1982 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR36)
    - Denmark, 1983-2003 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR37)
    - Denmark--Copenhagen, 1971-1997 and undated (Box EUR37)
    - Denmark--Destinations, 1968-1989 (Box EUR37)
    - Denmark--Hotels, 1978-1998 and undated (Box EUR37)
    - Denmark--Maps, 1985-2000 and undated (Box EUR37)
    - Finland--General, 1961-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR37)
    - Finland--Helsinki, 1964-186 and undated (Box EUR37)
    - Finland--Hotels, 1970-1999 and undated (Box EUR37)
    - Finland--Maps, 1961-1998 and undated (Box EUR38)
    - Finland--Vacation guides, 1983-1988 (Box EUR38)
    - Norway, 1960-2002 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR38)
    - Norway--Bergen, 1973-1986 and undated (Box EUR38)
    - Norway--Cruises/Voyages, 1983-2002 (Box EUR38)
    - Norway--Hotels, 1968-1996 and undated (Box EUR38)
    - Norway--My Travel Portfolio, 1986 (Box EUR38)
    - Norway--Oslo, 1985-1987 and undated (Box EUR38)
    - Sweden, 1967-2003 and undated (Box EUR38)
    - Sweden--Cruise lines, 1986-2000 (Box EUR39)
    - Sweden--Hotels, 1964-1997 and undated (Box EUR39)
    - Sweden--Maps, 1983-1997 and undated (Box EUR39)
    - Sweden--Stockholm, 1972-1998 and undated (Box EUR39)
    - Sweden--Sweden Traveler (publication), 1990-1995 (Box EUR39)
  - Spain, 139
    - General, 1960-1976 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR39)
    - General--Hotels, 1991-1998 and undated (Box EUR39)
    - General--Iberia Airlines planner, 1990 (Box EUR39)
    - General--Hiking/Ecotourism, 1988-1995 (Box EUR40)
    - General--Itineraries, 1980-2000 and undated (Box EUR40)
    - General--Jewish Spain, 1980-1994 (Box EUR40)
    - General--Maps, 1982-2000 and undated (Box EUR40)
    - General--Museum and monument guides, 1971-2005 and undated (Box EUR40)
    - General--Paradores, 1964-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR40)